Briana Santos

Home health aide

East Wareham, MA caynemartinez7_sem@indeedemail.com 5082735735

Hard worker. Very reliable. fast learner. Hands on type of person, I like to jump right into whatever it is I need to learn. I have been a certified home health aide for almost 2 years now, I've been doing care giver and home care work for going on 5. I'm very dependable, I love to work and I love what I do. I moved back to Massachusetts from Florida 1 year ago in August so my hours currently are open. I also am a certified MedTech. I also have years of experience in Waitressing, I've been actively working since I was 15 years old.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Receptionist

ABC Lawn Care - Port Charlotte, FL February 2013 to Present

Answering phone calls for my dads company, scheduling appointments, forwarding calls to other employees, giving estimates, entering Information into the computer, Perform other clerical receptionist duties such as filing, photocopying, collating, faxing etc

Server

Chili's - East Wareham, MA January 2019 to May 2019

Full time server at Chili's.

Caregiver

Heritage Oaks Assisted Living - Englewood, FL April 2018 to July 2018

I just moved back to Massachusetts so I'm looking for work ASAP. :)

Assisted living: toileting assisting with showers removing trash from each room making each bed in each room assisting residents with getting to and from the dining areas assisting residents get dressed every morning, assisting residents with care every step of the way if needed.

Home Health Aide

perez health care - Port Charlotte, FL March 2017 to June 2017

Working with special needs children. assisting with almost everyday needs. toileting, bathing, feeding, going to bed, waking up in the morning.. all of the everyday living needs someone would have i was doing for my clients.

Server

Olive Garden - Port Charlotte, FL September 2016 to February 2017

Greeting tables, Taking orders, Prepping Soups and Salads, dropping food to the table, checking on my guest to make sure the food and myself meet there expectations, boxing up food and dessert..etc

Home Health Aide (HHA)

The cubellis - Buzzards Bay, MA March 2015 to April 2016

Administer insulin, light house keeping, assisting with laundry, light cooking, give rides to the doctors.

Cashier/Food Handler

Aunte Annes - Port Charlotte, FL September 2015 to December 2015

Responsibilities

I do dishes, clean restrooms, run the store, close the store at nights as well as prep, and restocking.

Skills Used

My people person skills, flexibility and agility, and speedy service. Working full time hours.

Janitorial

BestPro Cleaning Services - North Port, FL January 2015 to April 2015

Cleaning Residential Homes, sweeping, mopping, dusting, vacuuming, bleaching, making beds, etc

Cashier

TJmaxx/Home goods - Wareham, MA January 2013 to December 2014

Sales Associate

Deluvia - Port Charlotte, FL Responsibilities

I sell a miracle aloe cream. I organize. Pack bags. Set up.

Accomplishments

I loved introducing people to an amazing product that truly works and being around people.

Skills Used

I put forth my outgoing personality to attract people to the product. I then use great communication skills to get people to trust the product and feel good about the purchase.

Education

Port Charlotte High School

Certifications and Licenses

Home Health Aide

Present

CMT

May 2018 to May 2019

TABC

CPR/First Aid

food handler certificate

Additional Information

Very motivated, People person and also a people pleaser, outgoing person, happy person, hands on learner, fast learner, multi tasker, good listener, reliable, trust worthy:)